fabathome.org 2019-07-12

# Privacy Policy - FabatHome

**Privacy Policy**

 **Last Updated: May 31 2018**

This Privacy Policy (“ **Policy** “) explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by fabathome.net (hereinafter referred to as “ **FabatHome** ,” “ **we** ,” “ **us** ,” or “ **our** ”). This Policy applies to FabatHome’ websites, including www.fabathome.net, or other online products or services (collectively, “ **Services** ”).

 **  1\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

We collect information about you in various ways when you use our Services. For example, we collect information you provide to us when you contact us or otherwise communicate with us. Such information may include your name, email address, and any other information you choose to provide. We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect on our Services.

When you access or use our Services, some information is automatically collected. For example, when you visit our Services through your computer, we automatically log your computer’s operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address and approximate location information derived from your IP address, access times, browser type and language, and the website you visited before navigating to our Services. Additionally, when you visit our Services through your mobile device, we collect your unique device ID, device make and model, device IP address, mobile web browser type and version and mobile carrier. We also collect information about your usage of and activity on our Services.

 **  a. Cookies**

We automatically collect information using “cookies.” Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. Among other things, cookies help us improve our Services and your experience. We use cookies to see which areas and features are popular and to count visits to our Services. In addition, third party links on our website may also contain cookies that recognize and/or place cookies on your browser. We do not control or utilize any cookies provided by such third parties.

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features of our Services.

 **  b. Web Beacons**

We may collect information using web beacons (also known as pixel tags). Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on our Services or in our emails. We use web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.

 **  c. Third Party Analytics and Advertisements.**

We may also allow third parties to provide analytics services and serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other devices or technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites and applications, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages or in apps, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by FabatHome and third parties to, among other things, analyze data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising or other content targeted to your interests and better understand the usage and visitation of our Services and other sites tracked by these third parties. For more information about Internet-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit [www.youronlinechoices.eu/](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

 **  2\. USE OF INFORMATION**

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to:

  * operate and improve our Services;
  * respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;
  * communicate with you about new promotions, upcoming events, and other news about products and services offered by FabatHome and our selected partners;
  * monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services;
  * personalize and improve the Services and provide advertisements, content or features that match user profiles or interests; and
  * carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.

 **  3\. SHARING OF INFORMATION**

We may share information about you as follows:

  * with your consent or at your direction;
  * with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers who are working on our behalf and need access to your information to carry out their work for us;
  * in response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with any applicable law, regulation or legal process, or as otherwise required by any applicable law, rule or regulation;
  * if we believe your actions are inconsistent with the spirit or language of our user agreements or policies or to protect the rights, property and safety of FabatHome or others; and
  * in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.
  * We may also share aggregated or de-identified information that cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

 **  4\. SECURITY**

FabatHome takes reasonable measures to help protect information we collect about you in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

 **  5\. DATA RETENTION**

We store the information we collect about you for as long as is necessary for the purpose(s) for which we originally collected it. We may retain certain information for legitimate business purposes or as required by law.

 **  6\. YOUR INFORMATION CHOICES AND CHANGES**

 **  a. Promotional Communications.**

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from FabatHome by following the instructions in those emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about updates to our Services.

 **  b. Your California Privacy Rights.**

California law permits residents of California to request certain details about how their information is shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please contact us at steven@fabathome.net. 

Alternatively, the law provides that a company may comply, as FabatHome does, by disclosing in its privacy policy that it provides consumers choice (opt-out or opt-in) regarding sharing personal information with third parties and affiliates for those third parties’ and affiliates’ direct marketing purposes, and information on how to exercise that choice. At this time, we do not share personal information with third parties or affiliates for those third parties’ or affiliates’ direct marketing purposes. However, if we do so in the future, FabatHome will provide you with a choice prior to sharing your personal information with third parties and affiliates for their direct marketing purposes. If you do not opt-in or if you do not choose to opt-out at the time FabatHome offers that choice, we will not share your information with that identified third party or affiliate for its direct marketing purposes.

 **  7\. RESIDENTS OF THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREAS**

If you are located in the European Economic Area (EEA):

 **  a. Controller of your Personal Data**

The controller of your personal data under this Privacy Policy Fabathome.net, with an address of Str. Banca Nationala nr. 25 ap. 7, Bacau, Romania.

 **  b. Legal Bases for Using Personal Data**

We process your personal data only if we have a legal basis to do so, including:

  1.     1. to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations;
    2. for the performance of our contract with you or to take steps at your request before entering into a contract;
    3. for our legitimate interests or those of a third party;
    4. where you have given consent to our specific use.

The purpose for which we use and process your information and the legal basis on which we carry out each type of processing is further explained below.

 **Purposes for which we will process information**|  **Legal Basis for the processing**  
---|---  
To respond to requests, questions, and comments, and provide other types of user support.| It is necessary for us to respond to requests, questions, and comments, and provide other types of user support in order to take steps at your request or according to the applicable contract between us.  
To offer you products and services in marketing communications, or direct you to portions of this Site or other websites, that we believe may interest you.| We may send electronic marketing communications to you if you have consented to these communications. It is in our legitimate interest to market out products and services to you by other means and to direct you to portions of the website or other websites that we believe may interest you. We consider this use to be proportionate and will not be prejudicial or detrimental to you.  
To carry out, evaluate, and improve our business (which may include developing new features for the website, analyzing and enhancing the user experience on the website; assessing the effectiveness of our marketing and advertising; and managing our communications.| It is in our legitimate interests to process your personal data to carry out these activities. We consider this use to be proportionate and will not be prejudicial or detrimental to you.  
To perform data analytics regarding usage of the website (including market and customer research, trend analysis, financial analysis, and anonymization of personal data).| It is in our legitimate interests to process your personal data to carry out these activities. We consider this use to be proportionate and will not be prejudicial or detrimental to you.  
To serve advertising, content and offers to you based on your interests and online activities, from us.| We will serve you advertising, content and offers to you based on your interests and online activities if you have consented to this processing.  
To enable our affiliates or service providers to perform certain activities on our behalf;| It is necessary for us to process your personal data in this manner in order to deliver the services and process transactions according to the applicable contract between us. It is also in our legitimate interest to enable our service providers and affiliates to perform certain activities on our behalf. We consider this use to be proportionate and will not be prejudicial or detrimental to you.  
To notify you of any changes to the website that may affect you.| It is necessary for us to process your personal data in order to deliver the services and process transactions according to the applicable contract between us.  
  
  * If we are required to do so by law, regulation, or legal process (such as a court order or subpoena);
  * In response to requests from government agencies, such as law enforcement authorities;
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity; and
  * In the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including a reorganization, dissolution, or liquidation)

| We conduct this processing to comply with our legal obligations and to protect the public interest.  
  
  * Guard against, identify, and prevent fraud and other criminal activity, claims, and other liabilities; and
  * Comply with applicable legal requirements, law enforcement requests, and our company policies.

| We conduct this processing to comply with our legal obligations and to protect the public interest.  
  
 **  c. International Transfers**

Some of our processing of your data may involve transferring your data outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). Some of our external third-party service providers are also based outside of the EEA, and their processing of your personal data will involve a transfer of data outside the EEA. This includes the United States. Where personal data is transferred to and stored in a country not determined by the European Commission as providing adequate levels of protection for personal data, we take steps to provide appropriate safeguards to protect your personal data, including when appropriate entering into standard contractual clauses approved by the European Commission, obliging recipients to protect your personal data.

 **  d. Retention of Personal Data**

We will retain your personal data only for as long as necessary for the purposes it was retained, such as to enable you to use the website and your products or to provide services to you. In some instances, we may retain data for longer periods in order to comply with applicable laws (including those regarding document retention), resolve disputes with any parties, and otherwise as necessary to allow us to conduct our business. All personal data we retain will be subject to this Policy and our internal retention guidelines.

 **  e. Data Subject Access Rights**

You have the following rights:

  * Right of access to your personal data: You have the right to ask us for confirmation on whether we are processing your personal data, and access to the personal data and related information.
  * Right to correction: You have the right to have your personal data corrected, as permitted by law.
  * Right to erasure: You have the right to ask us to delete your personal data, as permitted by law.
  * Right to withdraw consent: You have the right to withdraw consent that you have provided.
  * Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority: You have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority in the member state of your habitual residence.
  * Right to restriction of processing: You have the right to request the limiting of our processing under limited circumstances.
  * Right to data portability: You have the right to receive the personal data that you have provided to us, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, and you have the right to transmit that information to another controller, including to have it transmitted directly, where technically feasible.
  * Right to object: You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, as permitted by law, under limited circumstances.

In order to exercise any of these rights, please contact us according to the How to Contact Us section below. Please note that the above rights are not absolute and we may be entitled to refuse requests, wholly or partly, where exceptions under the applicable law apply.

 **  8\. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

FabatHome may change this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the Policy, and in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review this Policy whenever you access the Services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

 **  9\. HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at: steven@fabathome.net
